



Kanaalweg 36b 9422BC, Smilde



06 37205041



<u>Jurrien2013@gmail.com</u>



<u>LinkedIn</u> GitHub

### **SKILLS**

I am a hungry learner which loves to program and find solutions to all sorts of problems. I am trustworthy, punctual and can work independently as well as in a team ( Scrum was used in all teamwork ). I really enjoy building (web) applications and researching datasets. I am also very interested in all the complex components that make up the human body, especially microbiology, pathology and immunology.



# JURRIËN DE JONG

09/03/2002

## **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

April 2017 - Present

Jumbo Pepping Smilde, stock clerk

Jan 2021 - Sep 2021

Jumbo Pepping Smilde, grocery deliverer

Nov 2021 - Present

Jumbo Pepping Smilde, cashier

Sep 2021 - Present

Jumbo Pepping Smilde, fresh produce worker

### **EDUCATION**

**Dr. Nassaucollege Quintus, Assen (Including <u>Technasium</u>)** Aug 2014 – Juli 2019

**HBO Bioinformatics, Hanze hogeschool Groningen** Aug 2019 - Present

### **PROGRAMMING**

- ✓ Python (Including Snakemake)
- ✓ Java (Including Tomcat- and Springboot applications)
- √ F
- ✓ SQL
- ✓ Javascript (Including CSS and HTML)
- ✓ C# (basic knowledge)

### **LANGUAGES**

- Dutch ( native )
- ✓ English ( upper-intermediate )
- ✓ German (basic)
- ✓ French (basic)